[SPEAKER_01]: How can I satisfy all my desires?
[SPEAKER_00]: By overcoming the nature of desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's very much related to the previous question that you had about suffering.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, what people deem to be satisfaction of their desire, it's the result of the desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, by pursuing what you think satisfaction is, you cannot possibly satisfy the desire, in the sense of make it go away.
[SPEAKER_00]: It only covers it up and feeds it more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the desire is rooted, again, in your mental attitude.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which means, if you were to remove the desire from its roots, there won't be anything there to satisfy.
[SPEAKER_00]: There won't... there'll be no pressure for you, no nothing, no burden for you to have to chase and reach this goal and satisfy this displeasing feeling of an unsatisfied desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you can't.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what people don't realize.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't satisfy the displeasing feeling of a non-satisfied desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can only cover it up with a pleasing feeling of a non-satisfied desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Desire remains unsatisfied.
[SPEAKER_00]: The goal of desire is not to be satisfied.
[SPEAKER_00]: The goal of desire is to perpetuate its own nature of being a desire.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why, whether you're resisting pain or giving in to pleasure, you're maintaining the nature of your desires.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you remain bound by it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, if I want to go on holiday, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to go on holiday to the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you can either suffer,
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the circumstances are displeasing and you're trying to change them, or you can remove your desire to go to the Caribbean, and then you're at peace.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because you don't want to go in the first place.